[{"question": " janice has a question. who of the six of you has sleep with the six of you?", "answer": " wow, it\u0092s like a dirty math problem.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 1, "asentId": 2}, {"question": " i\u0092m sorry the answer there would be...none of us.", "answer": " come on over the years none of you ever y'know, got drunk and stupid.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 3, "asentId": 4}, {"question": " well, that\u0092s really a different question.", "answer": " i\u0092m sorry i find it hard to believe that a group of people who spends as much time together as you guys do has never bumped uglies.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 5, "asentId": 6}, {"question": " well, there was that one time that monica and rachel got together. monica and rachel: what?!!", "answer": " excuse me, there was no time!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 7, "asentId": 8}, {"question": " okay, but let\u0092s say there was. how might that go?", "answer": " okay, okay, well then answer me this. has any of you ever.... almost?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 9, "asentId": 10}, {"question": " does anybody need more coffee?", "answer": " yeah, i\u0092ll take some.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 11, "asentId": 12}, {"question": " oh, that is so unfortunate.", "answer": " what?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 15, "asentId": 16}, {"question": " cute naked guy is really starting to put on weight.", "answer": "  okay, i\u0092ll be back in just a minute. oh, phoebe i\u0092m sorry that i left lipstick marks on the phone.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 17, "asentId": 18}, {"question": " you didn\u0092t leave lipstick marks on the phone.", "answer": " oh, then it must\u0092ve been you. bye.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 19, "asentId": 20}, {"question": "  bye-bye!  that\u0092s why i moved out.", "answer": " hey, y'know while we\u0092re on that, when are you gonna tell my sister that you don\u0092t live here anymore.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 21, "asentId": 22}, {"question": " i think on some levels she already knows.", "answer": " phoebe, she doesn\u0092t know that you sneak out every night, she doesn\u0092t know that you sneak back every morning, and she doesn\u0092t know that you\u0092ve been living with your grandmother\u0092s for a week now.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 23, "asentId": 24}, {"question": " okay, well maybe not on those levels.", "answer": "  hey.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 25, "asentId": 26}, {"question": " hey.", "answer": " i\u0092m never gonna find a roommate, ever.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 27, "asentId": 28}, {"question": " why, nobody good?", "answer": " well let\u0092s see, there was the guy with the ferrets, that\u0092s plural. the spitter. oh-ho, and yes, the guy that enjoyed my name so much he felt the need to make a little noise every time he said it. nice to meet you, chandler bing bing! great apartment chandler bing, bing!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 29, "asentId": 30}, {"question": " so how many more do you have tomorrow?", "answer": " two. this photographer, who seemed really dull. and this actor guy, who i\u0092m not sure about, because when he called and i answered the phone \u0091chandler bing,\u0092 he said \u0091whoa-whoa, short message.\u0092", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 31, "asentId": 32}, {"question": "  ross , foot on the floor or come over no more!", "answer": "  sure, your dresser is missing but this she notices.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 33, "asentId": 34}, {"question": " what?", "answer": " i have to go. yeah, carol should be home by now, soo...", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 35, "asentId": 36}, {"question": " umm, how\u0092s it going with you guys?", "answer": " oh, better, actually. y'know i-i-i think i finally figured out why we were having so much trouble lately.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 37, "asentId": 38}, {"question": " oh, really?", "answer": " yeah, y'know how i have you guys, well she doesn\u0092t really have any close friends that are just hers, but last week she meet this woman at the gym, susan something, and they really hit it off, and i-i-i think it\u0092s gonna make a difference", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 39, "asentId": 40}, {"question": " soo, ah, eric, what kind of photography do ya do?", "answer": " oh, mostly fashion, so there may be models here from time to time, i hope that\u0092s cool.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 41, "asentId": 42}, {"question": " yes, that is cool. because i have models here y'know......never.", "answer": " oh, yeah, during the summer, i spend most weekends at my sister\u0092s beach house, which you are welcome to use by the way. although, i should probably tell you, she\u0092s a porn star.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 43, "asentId": 44}, {"question": "  bedroom. bathroom. living room. this right here is the kitchen, and thanks for coming by,  bye-bye.", "answer": " don\u0092t you ah, don\u0092t you wanna ask me any questions?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 47, "asentId": 48}, {"question": " sure. ummm. what\u0092s up?", "answer": " well, ah, i\u0092m an actor. i\u0092m fairly neat. i ah, i got my own tv. oh, and don\u0092t worry i\u0092m totally okay with the gay thing.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 49, "asentId": 50}, {"question": " what gay thing?", "answer": " ah, y'know just in general people being gay, thing. i\u0092m totally cool with that.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 51, "asentId": 52}, {"question": " hi.", "answer": " hey!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 55, "asentId": 56}, {"question": " hey, mon.", "answer": " hey-hey-hey. you wanna hear something that sucks.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 57, "asentId": 58}, {"question": " do i ever.", "answer": " chris says they\u0092re closing down the bar.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 59, "asentId": 60}, {"question": " no way!", "answer": " yeah, apparently they\u0092re turning it into some kinda coffee place.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 61, "asentId": 62}, {"question": " just coffee! where are we gonna hang out now?", "answer": " got me.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 63, "asentId": 64}, {"question": "  can i get a beer.", "answer": " hey, did you pick a roommate?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 65, "asentId": 66}, {"question": " you betcha!", "answer": " is it the italian guy?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 67, "asentId": 68}, {"question": " um-mm, yeah right!", "answer": " he\u0092s so cute.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 69, "asentId": 70}, {"question": " oh yes, and that\u0092s what i want a roommate that i can walk around with and be referred to as the funny one.", "answer": " oh look, the pool table\u0092s free. rack \u0091em up. i\u0092ll be back in just a minute. get ready for me to whip your butt.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 71, "asentId": 72}, {"question": " okay, but after that, we\u0092re shootin\u0092 some pool.", "answer": "   oh, um, no, no, no, no excuse me, hello. hi. my friend ordered an onion, not an olive, and uh i ordered a rum and diet coke, which i don\u0092t think this is.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 73, "asentId": 74}, {"question": " i am so sorry.", "answer": " that\u0092s all right.  i mean hard is it to get a couple drinks right, huh? friend no. 1: well, i would like to propose a toast to the woman, who in one year from today, become mrs. dr. barry farber dds", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 75, "asentId": 76}, {"question": " ummm, i think it\u0092s time to see the ring again.  friend no. 2: oh, isn\u0092t it exciting, i mean it\u0092s like having a boyfriend for life.", "answer": " yeah, i know. friend no. 1: what?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 77, "asentId": 78}, {"question": " oh, i don\u0092t know. well maybe it\u0092s just the idea of barry for the rest of my life. i don\u0092t know i think i feel like i need to have one last fling, y'know, just to sorta get it out of my system.  friend no. 1: rachel stop! friend no. 2: you\u0092re so bad!", "answer": " i\u0092m serious, i really, i think i need just to have some...meaningless, sex y'know, with the next guy that i see.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 79, "asentId": 80}, {"question": " excuse, i seem to have dropped my ball.", "answer": " yeah, so?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 81, "asentId": 82}, {"question": " oh my god, i went to high school with her.  rachel! hi!", "answer": " monica! look! hi! what do ya think?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 85, "asentId": 86}, {"question": " oh my god, you can\u0092t even see where the titanic hit it.", "answer": " yes, his name is barry, he\u0092s a doctor, thank you very much.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 87, "asentId": 88}, {"question": " awww, just like you always wanted. congratulations", "answer": " thank you. so how-how \u0091bout you, are-are you seeing anybody?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 89, "asentId": 90}, {"question": " aww, not right now.", "answer": " oh, but that\u0092s okay.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 91, "asentId": 92}, {"question": " i know.", "answer": " yeah.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 93, "asentId": 94}, {"question": " so, i\u0092ll get-get back to my friend.", "answer": " oh, yeah, sure, sure, sure, sure.  listen, can we please have lunch the next time i\u0092m in the city?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 95, "asentId": 96}, {"question": " oh, that\u0092d be great.", "answer": " okay!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 97, "asentId": 98}, {"question": " thanks.", "answer": " bye!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 99, "asentId": 100}, {"question": " no real-, honey, really it\u0092s fine, just g-go with susan. really, i, no, i think girls night out is a great idea. okay, okay, bye", "answer": " so what are they doing?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 103, "asentId": 104}, {"question": " i don\u0092t know, something girlie.", "answer": "  hey, you\u0092re early.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 105, "asentId": 106}, {"question": " what are you doing with the lamp?", "answer": " i\u0092m just taking it to be re-wired.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 107, "asentId": 108}, {"question": " no, no, mr. heckles no one is making any noise up here.", "answer": " you\u0092re disturbing my oboe practice.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 111, "asentId": 112}, {"question": " you don\u0092t play the oboe!", "answer": " i could play the oboe!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 113, "asentId": 114}, {"question": "  who are you?", "answer": " hi, i\u0092m eric, i\u0092m gonna be chandler\u0092s new roommate.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 117, "asentId": 118}, {"question": " i\u0092m chandler\u0092s new roommate.", "answer": " i-i-i don\u0092t think so.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 119, "asentId": 120}, {"question": " i could be chandler\u0092s new roommate.", "answer": " but, he told me over the phone.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 121, "asentId": 122}, {"question": " he told me in person.", "answer": " that\u0092s weird.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 123, "asentId": 124}, {"question": " hi, again.", "answer": " hey!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 127, "asentId": 128}, {"question": "  hey!", "answer": " thank you soo, much.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 129, "asentId": 130}, {"question": " you want some help with that?", "answer": " oh, no thanks, i got it.  no i don\u0092t!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 133, "asentId": 134}, {"question": " whoa! are you okay?", "answer": " whew! stood up to fast, got a little head rush.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 135, "asentId": 136}, {"question": " it\u0092s the heat.  and-and the humidity.", "answer": " that\u0092s a uh, that\u0092s a tough combination.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 137, "asentId": 138}, {"question": " do you wanna come in for some lemonade?", "answer": " like you wouldn\u0092t believe.  wow! this is a great place.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 139, "asentId": 140}, {"question": " thank you. just make yourself comfortable.", "answer": " gotcha.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 141, "asentId": 142}, {"question": " this place is really my grandmother\u0092s.  i got it from her when she moved to florida, otherwise i could never afford a place like this. so if the landlord ever asks, i\u0092m 87 year old woman, who\u0092s afraid of her vcr. so are you thirsty?", "answer": " oh, you bet i am!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 143, "asentId": 144}, {"question": " oh my god!!! what are you doing?!!", "answer": " you said, you wanna come in for some lemonade?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 147, "asentId": 148}, {"question": " so?!", "answer": " whoa, ah!! we\u0092re you just gonna give me some lemonade?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 149, "asentId": 150}, {"question": " yeah huh!! cover yourself up!", "answer": " oh right, right.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 151, "asentId": 152}, {"question": " i don\u0092t believe this! when someone asks you in for lemonade, and to you that means they wanna have sex?", "answer": " well usually...yeah! well, not just lemonade, iced tea, sometimes juice. well, sorry, i just, i thought you liked me. i\u0092m such a jerk.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 153, "asentId": 154}, {"question": " pheebs?", "answer": " huh?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 157, "asentId": 158}, {"question": " where\u0092s your bed?", "answer": " it\u0092s not in the apartment?  oh no. i can\u0092t believe this is happening again.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 159, "asentId": 160}, {"question": " what?", "answer": " okay, enough with the third degree! i-i\u0092ve, i don\u0092t live here anymore.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 161, "asentId": 162}, {"question": " what are you talking about?", "answer": " i\u0092m sorry, i-i-i-i don\u0092t live here anymore. i-i didn\u0092t know how to tell you, but y'know everybody else knows!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 163, "asentId": 164}, {"question": " everybody knows!", "answer": " that was supposed to be a good thing, i forget why. just listen, monica, i, do you know, okay, do you know, i couldn\u0092t sleep for like a month because i got like a dot of ink on one of the sofa cushions.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 165, "asentId": 166}, {"question": " well, you-you coulda just turned the cushion over.", "answer": " yeah, i would\u0092ve except i had a big spaghetti stain on the other side.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 167, "asentId": 168}, {"question": " what?!?!", "answer": " okay, this is what i\u0092m talking about, this. i-i need to live in a land where people can spill.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 169, "asentId": 170}, {"question": " you can spill. in the sink.", "answer": " aw, honey it\u0092s not your fault, y'know this is who you are, and i love you, and i want us to be friends, and if i keep living here i don\u0092t see that happening.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 171, "asentId": 172}, {"question": " i love you, too.", "answer": " aww, good.  what?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 173, "asentId": 174}, {"question": " what? i\u0092m just said.", "answer": " no you\u0092re not, you\u0092re wondering which cushion it is.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 175, "asentId": 176}, {"question": " so ah, whatcha watching?", "answer": " baywatch.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 177, "asentId": 178}, {"question": " what\u0092s it about?", "answer": " lifeguards.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 179, "asentId": 180}, {"question": " well, it sounds kinda stupid...  who\u0092s she?", "answer": " nicole eggert. you'll like her.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 181, "asentId": 182}, {"question": " wow! look at them run.", "answer": " they do that a lot. hey, you want a beer?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 183, "asentId": 184}, {"question": " yeah, i\u0092ll go get one.", "answer": " no, no, no, don\u0092t get up, i got a cooler right here.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 185, "asentId": 186}, {"question": " well, hello!", "answer": " hey.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 187, "asentId": 188}, {"question": " do you have any beers? we\u0092re out of beers.", "answer": "  help yourself.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 189, "asentId": 190}, {"question": " you okay?", "answer": " phoebe moved out.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 191, "asentId": 192}, {"question": " right.", "answer": " i don\u0092t understand, i mean am i so hard to live, is this why i don\u0092t have a boyfriend?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 193, "asentId": 194}, {"question": " noo!! you don\u0092t have a boyfriend because....i don\u0092t, i don\u0092t know why you don\u0092t have a boyfriend. you should have a boyfriend.", "answer": " well, i think so.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 195, "asentId": 196}, {"question": "  hi. where is everybody?", "answer": " oh, it\u0092s already closed, chris gave me the keys to lock up-what is wrong?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 199, "asentId": 200}, {"question": " my marriage, i think my marriage is um, is kinda over.", "answer": " oh no! why?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 201, "asentId": 202}, {"question": " \u0091cause carol\u0092s a lesbian.  and, and i\u0092m not one. and apparently it\u0092s not a mix and match situation.", "answer": " oh my god! i don\u0092t believe it! oh, you poor bunny.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 203, "asentId": 204}, {"question": "  i\u0092m an idiot. i mean shoulda seen it, i mean carol and i\u0092d be out and she\u0092d, she\u0092d see some beautiful woman, and, and she\u0092d be ross y'know look at her, and i\u0092d think, god, my wife is cool!", "answer": " aw! hey, do you think that susan person is her lover?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 205, "asentId": 206}, {"question": " well, now i do!!", "answer": " i\u0092m sorry.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 207, "asentId": 208}, {"question": " seven years. i mean we\u0092ve been together seven years, she\u0092s the only woman who\u0092s ever loved me, and the only woman i\u0092ve-i\u0092ve ever....", "answer": " aw, god ross. oh.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 209, "asentId": 210}, {"question": " umm, this is nice.", "answer": " i know, it is isn\u0092t it?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 211, "asentId": 212}, {"question": " no, i mean it, this feels really good. is it a hundred percent cotton?", "answer": " yeah! and i got it on sale, too.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 213, "asentId": 214}, {"question": " anyway, i should go, one of the lifeguards was just about to dismantle a nuclear device.", "answer": " well, if you wanna get a drink later we can.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 215, "asentId": 216}, {"question": " oh yeah, that sounds great.  oh, and listen, it\u0092s, it\u0092s gonna be....", "answer": " i know. thanks.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 217, "asentId": 218}, {"question": " maybe this would\u0092ve happened if i\u0092d been more nurturing, or i\u0092d paid more attention, or i... had a uterus. i can\u0092t believe this!", "answer": " i know no, no, y'know you don\u0092t deserve this, you don\u0092t ross. you\u0092re, you\u0092re really, you\u0092re so good.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 219, "asentId": 220}, {"question": " thanks.", "answer": " and you\u0092re so sweet.  and you\u0092re kind", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 221, "asentId": 222}, {"question": " wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.", "answer": " huh?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 225, "asentId": 226}, {"question": " wait, wait, wait.", "answer": " what?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 231, "asentId": 232}, {"question": " my foot is stuck in the pocket.", "answer": " what?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 233, "asentId": 234}, {"question": " no, i can\u0092t get it out.", "answer": " well, that\u0092s not something a girl wants to hear.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 235, "asentId": 236}, {"question": " no, come on don\u0092t start.  ouch!", "answer": " what?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 237, "asentId": 238}, {"question": " oh well. it probably would\u0092ve been the most constructive solution.", "answer": " you have chalk on your face.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 241, "asentId": 242}, {"question": " oh, ross you\u0092re right, i don\u0092t know why i always thought this was real grass.", "answer": " hey, are you okay?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 245, "asentId": 246}, {"question": " my wife\u0092s a lesbian.", "answer": " cool!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 247, "asentId": 248}, {"question": " i can\u0092t believe you came back.", "answer": " don\u0092t say anything. i don\u0092t wanna speak, i don\u0092t wanna think. i just want you to take me and kiss me and make love to me right here, right now.  friend no. 2: rachel! rachel!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 253, "asentId": 254}, {"question": " what? friend no. 2: you missed the exit!", "answer": " oh, sorry. friend no. 1: my god, what were you thinking about?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 255, "asentId": 256}, {"question": " um,  barry.", "answer": " awwww!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 257, "asentId": 258}]